Guide to the Charles Montague Bakewell Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1917-1920; Accession 2004-M-090
  - Research files
    - United States Government War Savings Manuals, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Warehouses [clipping], [ca. 1918] (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Workrooms -instruction and employment [Mrs. Springer's report], [ca. 1918] (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Workshops [Ouvroir-Laboratorio], [ca. 1918] (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Miscellaneous, 1918, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Oversize Broadsides [8 American Red Cross "Manifesti" in Italian] in Drawer 121, Room B57-A., [1917-1919] (Box 7, Folder 73)